♪ Your love is king♪
♪ Crown you in my heart♪
♪ Never need to part♪
♪ Your kisses ring...♪
Feel like we should maybe
slow down a little bit.
♪ Touching the very part of me♪
♪ It's making my soul sing♪
♪ Tearing the very heart
of me...♪
Supposed to be a turn-off soon.
♪ Your love is king...♪
You don't think we missed it?
Nah, I think we're good.
♪ You're the ruler of my heart♪
♪ Your kisses ring...♪
Here he is.
♪ Round and round
and round my.♪
Hey, Earn.
- Welcome, welcome. You made it.
- Thank you, thank you.
Hey, I'm gonna ask
that you come down here
at five miles per hour.
You know, there's kids and dogs
running around,
sometimes deer.
Yeah, yeah. Sorry.
So, when you pass this road,
just look on either side
for signs
to point you
where you need to go.
I got you booked
for entire grounds.
Great.
- Oh, is that the birthday girl?
- Yeah,
that's-that's Lottie.
This is Van.
Hi.
Beautiful family.
Well, I hope y'all enjoy.
Need anything, don't hesitate
to holler at me or my wife.
- Thank you, bye.
- All right, thank you.
Happy birthday.
- Very nice.
- Yeah.
Here, you want
to carry one of these?
Take the best one.
Ooh, purple.
That's Prince's favorite color.
What do you think
are the chances that
that guy's gonna
kill us in our sleep?
Honestly?
Eight.
Eight percent.
You think eight percent?
Sounds high.
It's a big tarp.
Yeah.
I got, uh...
I got a really awesome tent.
It's, like,
the most expensive one in REI.
The... the guy was like,
this is the best one they had.
Like, uh, I think
it's, like, a 12-person.
Like, uh...
It's for how many people?
12 person, and you can
split the rooms,
and it has, like, a porch, too.
We're gonna be freezing.
What?
'Cause if you don't have
enough body heat to insulate
the... space...
It'll be fine, though.
Okay.
- It'll be fine.
I'm-I'm excited.
- I'm-I'm sorry.
- No, no, no. Okay.
- I didn't know.
- It looks really nice. I mean...
- Okay. You're...
very welcome.
We're gonna... I'm gonna get...
It's kind of big.
- Let's find the corners.
- Hey, Lottie, you want
to-you want to help us?
No.
Huh.
What's going on with her?
She's just tired.
She'll be fine.
Can you hand me those?
Um, this?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
No problem.
So, have you...
thought more about L.A.?
I mean...
Yeah, I've thought
about it a lot, actually.
We were gonna talk about it
a little later.
Yeah.
Whenever you want.
Those ones, I think,
go by the door.
Hmm.
Are we missing a pole?
Doesn't quite look right.
What do you think?
She loves it.
Which room you gonna sleep in?
Hm... this one.
Ooh.
Which one's Daddy
gonna sleep in?
He can sleep outside.
Outside?
I'll get my toothbrush.
I peed.
That's great.
That's exactly what
we were supposed to do.
This river's too high.
- We can't cross it.
- I think we can...
We can make it across here.
I think there's a lo-log
underneath there.
We could hop to that rock.
Oh... you think
she can cross that?
We're just gonna get wet.
- It's too high.
- We'll get wet up to here, but
- she can get on my shoulders.
- Earn. No.
She can get on my shoulders.
Come on, Lottie, let's go.
We can't cross this.
- You don't think so?
- No.
- Maybe...
- That... that-that's
all gonna collapse.
It's all gonna collapse.
That's not true.
- Is it?
- Not in Europe.
- All right.
- It's hard there.
You enjoying
your birthday, Lottie?
Do we have any other snacks?
Yeah, I think we do.
- It's like I'm not here.
- I don't really like
my birthday.
Since when?
What kind of six-year-old
doesn't enjoy their birthday?
You know how she is
when she's in her moods.
You can't catch anything?
Don't worry, we're gonna go
catch fish later,
and then tonight we're
gonna try to catch a snipe.
A snipe?
Yeah.
We're gonna go snipe hunting.
What's a snipe?
It's this really rare creature.
It's nearly extinct.
And it only comes out at night
when the moon is out,
and it's really crazy long,
and it has red eyes.
But only the coolest
and the smartest can catch it.
Did you ever catch it?
No, but maybe
with your help I can.
I want to catch it.
Yeah, we're gonna try.
Are y...
are you pranking our daughter?
You don't know
what a snipe hunt is?
- No.
- It's, like, a tradition.
I did it at Girl Scouts.
You were in Girl Scouts?
- I did not know that.
- Yeah.
I did it for just a summer,
when I was eight.
I didn't like being trapped
camping with people
I didn't vibe with, so...
...I think, is actually a bird
that's hard to catch,
or something like that,
and it turned
into this folklore,
so, you could, in the end,
we could tell her it's a bird.
Okay.
- You want to...
- I have no problem with
doing it. It sounds... sounds
like it could be, uh, fun.
You know, cool,
it's just, when you-when you
- first hear "snipe hunt"...
- Mm-hmm.
it sounds like a racist,
- like, mob.
- Oh, my God.
Like, "Let's get the snipe.
- You're so silly.
- He's taking our jobs."
Hey!
Oh.
- Lottie. You...
- Wow.
- Maybe put him down.
- Yeah, put him down.
- Yeah, maybe put him dow...
- I don't want to, though.
Lottie.
This is nature, okay?
That toad is not for you, okay?
I want to hold it, though.
- I want it to stay.
- Yeah.
But it let you
take a look at him,
and then it wanted to go.
You should feel lucky that
you got to hold it, okay?
Come on.
I have some raspberries.
You know, I know
this little girl.
Her name is, uh, Shottie.
And, um,
she has a dad named Shmad.
And, um...
all they do is eat ice cream
in Opposite World.
What?
All they do is eat ice cream,
and they get thinner.
That's, like,
totally the opposite
of what you're supposed to do.
- What would be the...
- You're sup...
you're supposed to not have
- Ice cream.
- ice cream all the time,
and when you do,
you're supposed to get fat.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Is that why I'm so fat?
I eat ice cream,
like, every day.
Like, for breakfast.
- No, you don't.
- I do.
You guys good?
- Yeah, we're good.
- Yeah.
All right.
- I love how calm it is.
- Yeah, it's great.
- Oh, that
actually is cool.
- It's really cool.
I wish grandma
and grandpa were here.
Hmm.
- Yeah, that makes sense.
- Yeah.
You know, we'll make sure
that, um,
they celebrate with us
this weekend.
- Yeah.
Are you just missing them
or you wish they were doing
your birthday with you?
- Both.
Both.
Well, I think it's...
kind of cool that we're all...
- Together. Yeah.
- together. Yeah.
That's special.
That's special, too, right?
I mean,
- it doesn't happen all the time.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Am I starving,
or is this incredible?
It's really good.
I think we should
talk more about L.A.
Yeah.
We probably should.
Mom.
The moon is out.
Oh, it is.
Baby, why don't we go looking
for snipes tomorrow, hm?
I think it's a little late now.
Here, take the pillowcase,
put it on the ground,
and open it up.
Do you have a marshmallow?
- Just one?
- Yeah.
And you're gonna take
the marshmallow,
you're gonna put it
inside the pillowcase
all the way to the end, okay?
Now, you're gonna
take the lantern,
you're gonna put it
next to the opening,
so that when the snipe walks in,
you can see it.
You need to find a stick. Here.
And then you're gonna
make this sound.
That's gonna lure
the snipe, okay?
And the snipe should just
walk in on its own
to get the marshmallow bait.
You know what you're
gonna do when it does that?
You're gonna take your foot,
you're gonna stomp
on the pillowcase,
trap the snipe in there,
and then you're gonna
hit it on the head, okay?
Okay.
Here.
Good job.
All right, baby, have fun.
Where are you going?
Aw. Baby, you have to
hunt the snipe alone.
If there's
too many people around,
the snipe's not gonna come.
But don't worry,
we're right over there, okay?
What?
You, what?
L.A.
You gonna come with me?
Is that why you did all this?
What do you mean?
You know, it feels
a little manipulative
to rent out
an entire campground.
I-I just wanted to make
Lottie's birthday special.
Can I ask you a question?
What's so great about Atlanta...
...that you can't
leave it behind?
I mean, it'd be
my choice to stay.
That's not what
it's about, though.
I'm afraid that...
it's about you not wanting
to be alone when you go there,
and that you're scared of that.
And I'm... not just
your security blanket.
Got him!
What?
I got the snipe.
Uh... what did it look like?
Long, with red eyes,
and I hit it with the stick
when I caught it.
Uh, okay, okay,
Lottie, um...
listen.
When I count to three,
you're going to put
the lamp down very slowly,
drop the bag,
and run to Mommy, okay?
- Okay.
One, two...
- three. Come, come, come,
come, come, come, come,
- Go, go, go, go,
- go, go.
- Come, come, come.
Baby, are you okay?
Hold this.
Earn...
- Please be careful.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Aah!
- Oh, my God.
Oh! Oh!
- What was that?
It was a snipe.
I got him.
VAN and EARN:
♪ Happy birth...♪
Shh! No singing, please.
Happy birthday, baby.
Happy birthday. so big.
Earn.
Yeah?
Is that your teeth chattering?
Maybe.
I... I think you should
just get in with us.
This is really sad.
Her feet are cold.
- Her feet?
- Yeah.
Yeah...
It's those sharp toenails.
I know. Talons.
Lottie?
Lottie, do you want
some more s'mores?
What are you doing?
Testing to see if she's awake.
You know, when I go...
...I-I wouldn't
have to be alone.
You know, I'm not...
I'm not saying that to be cocky.
I have a good job, and a...
cool job.
I'm not terrible-looking.
And I'm not tied to anything
that would
turn someone off from me.
And you'd be here,
raising our kid.
And I'd see you every, you know,
couple of months,
maybe once or twice a year.
If I didn't want to be alone,
I wouldn't have to be.
I could find someone.
You know, someone new, but...
it-it's not about that.
Then what is it about?
Is it, like, a...
a co-parenting arrangement
- or...
- No. I, uh...
I want to be a family.
I want us to be a family.
I mean, look at Lottie.
I mean, she's fucking amazing.
She's the physical manifestation
of what happens
when we get together.
I mean, she's smart,
she's kind, she's sensitive,
and she's intuitive.
- Mm-hmm.
- She's...
the best... parts of
both of us. I'm just...
I...
I know you love Lottie, and...
...I know you'll miss her.
I'm fighting for you, Van.
You know me.
I don't fight for anything.
Van, look at me.
I love you.
I can't just pack up
my whole life
'cause you love me
as Lottie's mom.
That's not...
enough...
for me.
Do you think I just
see you as Lottie's mom?
Do you not realize how...
in love with you I am?
How much I think about you?
I've dreamed about you
every night since Amsterdam.
I do see you as a woman.
I still want you.
I desire you, Van.
When I think about
the fact that...
that you are also
the mother of my child...
...I could just fucking burst.
I've never felt that way
about anything.
I wasn't able...
I wasn't able
to feel that before.
And I'll love you forever
because of that, no matter what.
I mean, what else
are we doing this for...
...if not for that feeling?
What else is there?
You know what I mean?
I do.
It's... a little...
...Kanye being passionate,
but I do know what you mean.
I don't want to find
someone new.
Not because it's...
it isn't time-consuming, and...
you know, annoying,
which it is.
It's because...
I... I just want
to do this with you.
Okay? I just want
Will you go to L.A. with me,
so we can be a family?
Like, a for-real family?
Okay... Okay.
Okay.
Are you cold?
- Yeah, I'm freezing.
- Okay.
I love you, too.
I know.
Me too.
I think there's a slant.
I think we slid down.
Mm!
Now you spit.
Supposed to rain today.
What?
When?
Leave it.
We'll-we'll get another.
Okay. Come on.
- Baby, come on, let's go.
- Yeah, let's get in the car.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
♪ I won't pretend♪
♪ I'm good at forgiving♪
♪ But I can't hate you♪
♪ Though I have tried♪
♪ I still really, really
love you♪
♪ Love is stronger than pride♪
♪ I still really, really
love you♪
♪ I won't pretend♪
♪ That I intend to stop living♪
♪ I'm good at forgiving♪
♪ But I can't hate you♪
♪ Although I have tried♪
♪ I still really, really
love you♪
♪ Love is stronger than pride♪
♪ I still really, really
love you.♪
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH